Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco Papers
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Music, 1905-1968 (Box 1-106)
  - Works with opus number, 1910-1968
    - Op. 204: The book of Tobit (narrator, voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box 84)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 85/1-2)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 85/3)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript short score (Box 86)
      - Parts (Box 57-61)
    - Op. 204: Thanksgiving (voices, piano)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 62/1)
    - Op. 205: Sonatina (flute, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 62/2)
    - Op. 205?: Quartetto (violin, viola, violoncello, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score fragment; [1] p. (Box-folder 62/3)
    - Op. 206: Eclogues (flute, English horn, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 164
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 87/1)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 87/1)
      - Parts (Box-folder 87/1)
    - Op. 206?: Symphony no. 1
      - Holograph manuscript full score, Unfinished (Box-folder 87/2)
    - Op. 207: The divan of Moses-Ibn-Ezra (voice, guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 154
      - Printed score (Box-folder 62/4)
    - Op. 208: Sonata (violoncello, harp)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 62/5)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 87/3)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 87/3)
      - Violoncello part (Box-folder 87/3)
    - Op. 209: Rhapsody: the harp of David (harp)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 157
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 62/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 62/7)
    - Op. 210: Appunti. Quaderno primo (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 62/8)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 87/4)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 62/9)
    - Op. 210: Appunti. Quaderno secundo (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 62/10)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 87/5)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 62/11)
    - Op. 210: Appunti. Quaderno terro; Quaderno quarto (guitar)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores, Unfinished; Laid in: Holograph manuscript fragments, lists of titles, and notes; [11] p. (Box-folder 62/12)
  - Works without opus number, 1905-1967
    - 2 canons (piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 89/1)
    - 2 canti greci (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 64
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 89/2)
    - 2 lyriche dal Giardiniere (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 122
    - 2 madrigali a Galatea (chorus)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score (Box-folder 89/3)
    - 3 canti all'aria aperta (violin, piano)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores, Laid in: holograph manuscript note; [1] p. (Box-folder 89/4)
    - 3 chansons grises (voice, piano)
      - 2 holograph manuscript piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 89/5)
    - Above suspicion [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 89/6)
    - Address unknown [film, Columbia,1944]
      - 5 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 89/7)
    - All night long (voice, piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 89/8)
    - America marching on [film, MGM, 1937]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 89/9)
    - An American rhapsody (orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full1 score (Box-folder 98/1)
      - Photocopied manuscript short score (Box-folder 98/1)
    - Arie antiche (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 89/10)
    - Bad bascomb [film, MGM, 1946]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 89/11)
    - Ballade des amantes celebres (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 101
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 89/11)
    - Ballata dall'Esilio
      - Manuscript and printed score (Box-folder 89/12)
    - Bas-relief (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, see ML96.C34 no. 2
    - Bataan [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 89/13)
    - La battaglia è finita (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 89/14)
    - Billy the kid [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 2 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 89/15)
    - Bitter lemons (women's voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 89/16)
    - The brave bulls [film, Columbia, 1951]
      - 10 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 89/17)
    - The brigand [film, Columbia, 1952]
      - Photocopied manuscript short score, Laid in: typescript list of cues; [37] p. (Box-folder 98/2)
    - Calma a giramonte (piano)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores (Box-folder 90/1)
    - The Canterville ghost [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 2 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 90/2)
    - La canzone della tombola (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/3)
    - La canzone di usigliano (voice, piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/4)
    - Cera vergine (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/5)
    - Chanson à boire (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 61
    - Le chant des tenebres (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/6)
    - Cherry ripe (voices)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal rehearsal score, see ML96.C34 no. 163
      - Printed vocal rehearsal score (Box-folder 90/7)
    - Children's song (voice, piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Laid in: poem "Firenze" by Ulric De Vaere, 1965; 2 p. (Box-folder 90/8)
    - Clarinet quintet (Clarinet, string quartet)
      - Holograph manuscript score fragment; [1] p., Unfinished (Box-folder 90/9)
    - The clock [film, MGM, 1945]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 90/10)
    - Le columbe (voice, piano)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/11)
    - Concerto (violoncello, orchestra)
      - Printed full score (Box-folder 90/12)
    - The crime doctor's courage [film, Columbia, 1945]
      - 8 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 90/13)
    - Dangerous business [film, Columbia, 1946]
      - 11 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 90/14)
    - The day of the fox [film, UPA, 1956]
      - 9 photocopied holograph manuscript score excerpts (Box-folder 90/15)
    - De amico ad amicam (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 90/16)
    - Double concerto (violin, violoncello, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, Unfinished (Box-folder 91/1)
    - Down to earth [film, Columbia, 1947]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 91/2)
    - Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Hyde [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 91/3)
    - Dubarry was a lady [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 6 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 91/4)
    - Due liriche dal Giardiniere di Tagore (voice, piano)
      - 2 holograph manuscript piano-vocal scores (Box-folder 91/5)
    - English suite (piano or harpsichord)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 18
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 91/6)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 91/6)
    - Étoile filante (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 78
      - Printed score (Box-folder 91/7)
    - Everybody does it [film, Fox, 1949]
      - 1 photocopied holograph manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 91/8)
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 91/8)
    - Exotica (violin, piano)
      - 3 holograph manuscript scores, see also ML96.C34 no. 48 (Box-folder 91/9-10)
    - Fanfare (organ)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 92/1)
    - Fingers at the window [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 92/2)
    - Fiori di loto (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 92/3)
    - For our vines have tender grapes [film, MGM, 1945]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/4)
    - For the living [broadcast, American Cancer Society, 1949]
      - 8 holograph manuscript score excerpts (Box-folder 92/5)
    - Forgotten treasures [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 1 holograph manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 92/6)
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 92/6)
    - Fuga elegiaca (2 guitars)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores, Laid in: Holograph manuscript sketch; [1] p. (Box-folder 92/7)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 92/8)
    - Galop: homage to Offenbach
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt, MGM film sketch (Box-folder 92/9)
    - Gaslight [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 2 holograph manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/10)
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/10)
    - Genesis suite. The flood: Noah's ark (narrator, chorus, orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph mansucript full score (Box-folder 98/3)
    - Half pint kid [i.e. Harrigan's kid] [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/11)
    - The hangman [i.e. Hitler's madman] [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 5 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/12)
    - The heavenly body [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/13)
    - Hold high the torch [i.e. Courage of Lassie] [film, MGM, 1946]
      - 7 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/14)
    - Homage to Paderewski (piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 92/15)
    - I love a mystery [film, Columbia, 1945]
      - 9 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/16)
    - Inca gold [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 92/17)
    - Journey for Margaret [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 92/18)
    - Jubilee songs
      - 5 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts, MGM film sketches (Box-folder 92/19)
    - Keeper of the flame [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 3 holograph manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 93/1)
      - 8 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 93/1)
    - Kismet [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt, Laid in: typescript list of cues; [1] p. (Box-folder 93/2)
    - Kol nidre (violoncello, piano)
      - Photocopied manuscript score (Box-folder 93/3)
    - Kol nidrei (violoncello, organ)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 93/4)
    - Kol nidrei (voice)
      - 2 holograph manuscript vocal scores (Box-folder 93/5)
    - Lassie come home [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 2 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 93/6)
    - Liberty, mother of exiles (chorus, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 93/7)
    - Il libro di Dulcina (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 93/8)
    - The loves of Carmen [film, Columbia, 1948]
      - Photocopied manuscript short score, Laid in: typescript / holograph manuscript list of cues; [32] p. (Box-folder 98/4-5)
      - Photocopied manuscript short score (Box-folder 99/1)
    - Lucertolina (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 58
      - Printed score (Box-folder 93/9)
    - A lullaby on Foster's themes (voices, orchestra)
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 99/2)
    - The mark of the whistler [film, Columbia, 1944]
      - 2 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 93/10)
    - The mask of the avenger [film, Columbia, 1951]
      - Photocopied manuscript short score, Laid in: typescript list of cues; [8] p. (Box-folder 99/3-4)
    - Meditation (violoncello, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 93/11)
      - Violoncello part (Box-folder 93/11)
    - Mi-la (piano)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 93/12)
    - Mission 36 [i.e. The black parachute] [film, Columbia, 1944]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts, Laid in: typescript list of cues; [6] p. (Box-folder 93/13)
    - Movie sketches [MGM]
      - 32 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 93/14)
    - Mrs. Parkington [i.e. The Parkington] [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 6 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 93/15)
    - Music on the waters (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 60
    - My love's like a red rose (voice, piano)
      - 1 photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 93/16)
    - Naaritz'cho (cantor, chorus, organ)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 97
    - Napolitana (2 pianos)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 94/1)
    - Night editor [film, Columbia, 1946]
      - 9 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 94/2)
    - Ninna-nanna: berceuse (piano)
      - Printed score, Program with notes and early Mario Castelnuovo-Tedesco photograph (Box-folder 94/3)
    - Ninna-nanna del Dopoguerra (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 62
      - Printed score (Box-folder 94/4)
    - Nocturne in Hollywood (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 94/5)
    - Norwegian sketches
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts, MGM film sketches (Box-folder 94/6)
    - Once upon a Thursday [i.e. The affairs of Martha] [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 94/7)
    - Ouvertures per il teatro di Shakespeare. Hamlet
      - Holograph manuscript full score, Unfinished (Box-folder 99/5)
    - Ouvertures per il teatro di Shakespeare. Othello
      - Holograph manuscript full score, Unfinished (Box-folder 99/6)
    - The owl (voices, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 94/8)
      - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 94/8)
    - Paraphrases on Foster's songs
      - 3 holograph manuscript full score excerpts, MGM film sketches (Box-folder 94/9)
      - 8 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 94/9)
    - Picture of Dorian Gray [film, MGM, 1945]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 94/10)
    - Plan for destruction [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 2 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 94/11)
    - Prayers my grandfather wrote (organ or piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 156
      - Photocopied holograph manuscript score, Laid in: photocopied melody book by Bruno Senigaglia used during composition (Box-folder 94/12)
      - Photocopied printed score (Box-folder 94/12)
    - Prelude on a twelve-tone row (organ)
      - Holograph manuscript score, Based on his Preludio e fanfara; see also ML96.C34 no. 130 (Box-folder 94/13)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 94/13)
    - Preludio e fanfara (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 130
      - Holograph manuscript score, Fanfara is incomplete; Part of Dodici studi dodecafonici (Box-folder 94/14)
      - Printed score (Box-folder 94/14)
    - Preludio su L'Annunciarione (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 131
    - Primavera fiorentina (piano)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores, Laid in: photocopies of inspirational paintings; [1] p. (Box-folder 95/1)
    - Prison ship [film, Columbia, 1945]
      - 11 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 95/2)
    - Rage in Heaven [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 95/3)
    - Rationing [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 95/4)
    - Regina Giovanna di F. Mistral: Act II, scene 4 (orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score (Box-folder 95/5)
    - El retablo de las Meravillas: a fantasy after Cervantes (guitar)
      - Holograph manuscript score, Unfinished (Box-folder 95/6)
    - Return of the vampire [film, Columbia, 1943]
      - 12 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 95/7)
    - Reunion in France [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 2 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 95/8)
    - The rogues of Sherwood Forest [film, Columbia, 1950]
      - 7 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts, Laid in: typescript list of cues; [6] p. (Box-folder 95/9)
    - Ronde des fruits (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 134
    - Ronde des livres (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 135
    - Rumors [i.e. Mr. Blabbermouth] [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 95/10)
    - Russia [i.e. Song of Russia] [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 95/11)
    - Scampanio (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 95/12)
    - Scenic grandeur [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 1 holograph manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 95/13)
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 95/13)
    - Scottish suite
      - 6 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts, MGM film sketches (Box-folder 95/14)
    - La sera fiesolana (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see also ML96.C34 no. 59 (Box-folder 95/15)
    - Shadowed [film, Columbia, 1946]
      - 6 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 95/16)
    - She's a soldier too [film, Columbia, 1944]
      - 5 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 96/1)
    - Somewhere I'll find you [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 96/2)
    - Son of Lassie [film, MGM, 1945]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 96/3)
    - Spring (voice, piano)
      - 1 photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 96/4)
    - The stars look down [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 96/5)
    - Step this way [i.e. The big store] [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 96/6)
    - Strictly dishonorable [film, MGM, 1951]
      - 1 holograph manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 96/7)
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 96/7)
    - Tavern (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 96/8)
    - Tell tale hands [i.e. Main Street after dark] [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 96/9)
    - Terrazze (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score (Box-folder 96/10)
    - A thousand shall fall [i.e. The cross of Lorraine] [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 4 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 96/11)
    - Three little songs (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Dialogue is a photocopied holograph (Box-folder 96/12)
    - Time out of mind [film, Universal, 1947] (piano, orchestra)
      - Photocopied manuscript short score, Co-written by Miklos Rozsa (Box-folder 96/13)
      - Photocopied manuscript short score excerpts, Includes Symphony finale, an early version of New England Symphony (Box-folder 96/14)
    - Toccata con jazz (piano, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript short score, Unfinished (Box-folder 97/1)
    - Tonight we dance [i.e. Dancing in Manhattan] [film, MGM, 1944]
      - 6 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 97/2)
    - Tortilla flat [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 5 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 97/3)
    - Tulip time in Michigan [i.e. Seven sweethearts] [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 3 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 97/4)
    - Two Byron songs (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 97/5)
      - Photocopied manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 97/5)
    - Two Kipling songs (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score (Box-folder 97/6)
    - Two-man submarine [film, Columbia, 1944]
      - 14 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts (Box-folder 97/7)
    - Un madrigale di Michelangelo (chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript short score (Box-folder 97/8)
    - Valse triste: homage to Sibelius
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt, MGM film sketches (Box-folder 97/9)
    - The vanishing Virginian [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 1 holograph manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/10)
    - Vendetta against a dictator [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/11)
    - Villa sola (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, see ML96.C34 no. 149
      - Printed score (Box-folder 97/12)
    - Violin concerto no. 3 (violin, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript sketches; [18] p. (Box-folder 97/13)
    - Le voyage (voice, piano)
      - Holograph manuscript piano-vocal score, Laid in: song text, with additional text of poem "The nightingale" by Frère Joseph and François du Trembley; [2] p. (Box-folder 97/14)
    - We were dancing [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/15)
    - When ladies meet [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript score excerpt (Box-folder 97/16)
    - Whistling in Brooklyn [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/17)
    - White cargo [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/18)
    - Who's superstitious? [film, MGM, 1943]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/19)
    - The Winter's tale (voices, chorus, orchestra)
      - Holograph manuscript full score, Unfinished (Box-folder 99/7)
      - Holograph manuscript short score, Unfinished (Box-folder 99/7)
    - A woman's face [film, MGM, 1941]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/20)
    - A Yank at Eton [film, MGM, 1942]
      - 1 photocopied manuscript short score excerpt (Box-folder 97/21)
    - The yearling [film, MGM, 1946]
      - 5 photocopied manuscript short score excerpts, Laid in: typescript list of cues; [3] p. (Box-folder 97/22)
    - [Unidentified] (piano; 1936, undated)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores (Box-folder 100/1)
    - Unidentified (piano)
      - Holograph manuscript score, Unfinished (Box-folder 100/2)
    - Unidentified (piano; 1945, 1955)
      - 2 holograph manuscript scores, Incomplete (Box-folder 100/3)
    - Unidentified (piano, unspecified instrument/voice)
      - Manuscript score, Incomplete (Box-folder 100/4)
    - Unidentified (piano, 3 unspecified instruments/voices)
      - Holograph manuscript score, Incomplete (Box-folder 100/4)
    - Unidentified (voices)
      - Holograph manuscript vocal score, Sacred text (Box-folder 100/5)
    - Unidentified
      - Sketches and fragments; [11] p. (Box-folder 99/8)
    - Unidentified
      - Sketches and fragments; [47] p., Laid in: folder with manuscript notes; [1] p. (Box-folder 100/6)
    - Unidentified
      - Fragments; [7] p. (Box-folder 100/7)
    - Unidentified
      - Fragments; [5] p. (Box-folder 100/8)
  - Arrangements, before 1940-1967
    - Anonymous
      - Three Sephardic songs (voice, piano or harp)
        - Holograph manuscript score, see ML96.C34 no. 81
        - Printed piano-vocal score (Box-folder 100/9)